Rajesh K

Gold Appraiser and Gold Loan Sales - Assistant Manager Grade With above 7 Years Experience in Gold Loan.

Thanjavur, Tamil Nadu 614601 rajeshkanagarajan263_2ri@indeedemail.com +91 97877 98780

To secure a challenging position where I can effectively contribute my skills as Professional, possessing

competent Technical Skills, for the growth of industry given opportunity and prove my credential, candidature as well.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 1986-01-05 Eligible to work in: India

Highest Career Level: 5+ years experience

Industry: Banking & Finance
Total years of experience: 8

Work Experience

Senior Business Development Manager

Unimoni Financial Services Ltd - Pattukkottai, Tamil Nadu November 2021 to December 2023

- 1. Gold Loan Sales
- 2. GOLD APPRAISING

Gold Appraiser

IIFL Finance Ltd April 2017 to September 2021

1. GOLD APPRAISER

Assistant Branch Head

Manappuram Finance Ltd April 2015 to April 2017

Education

M.C.A in Computer Applications

Prist University

July 2011

Sri Venkateshwara College of arts & Science - Peravurani, Tamil Nadu July 2009

S.S.L.C

Govt. Boys, H.S. School - Pattukkottai, Tamil Nadu March 2004

B.C.A in Bachelor of Computer Applications

Prist University - Thanjavur, Tamil Nadu

Bharathidasan University - Tiruchchirappalli, Tamil Nadu

Skills / IT Skills

• GOLD LOAN